YICHI ZHANG

+1(734)800-6032 ♦ yichiz@umich.edu ♦ Website: https://yichiz97.github.io/ 3427 North Quad, 510 State St., Ann Arbor, MI 48109, U.S.A.

SUMMARY

Ph.D. candidate with research focuses on the intersection between computer science and economics, in particular, information elicitation and aggregation, mechanism design and their interactions with machine learning. Comfortable in using programming and mathematical tools to solve multi-agent problems including crowd-sourcing, peer grading, recommender system and machine learning with noisy labels.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Umich)

Sep 2019 - Present

Ph.D. in School of Information Advisor: Prof. Grant Schoenebeck

Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU)

Aug 2015 - Jun 2019

B.S. in Electronic Science and Engineering Advisor: Prof. Xinbing Wang and Prof. Luoyi Fu

University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA)

Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

CSST (summer research program), Department of Computer Science

Advisor: Prof. Mario Gerla

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCES

Research Assistant,	University of Michigan
Algorithm Engineer	Intern, YITUTech

Sep 2019 - Present Feb 2019 - May 2019

PUBLICATIONS AND PROJECTS

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

WWW'21

Grant Schoenebeck, Fang-Yi Yu and Yichi Zhang (ranked by alphabet)

- Propose a framework of using robust learning algorithms to design robust peer prediction mechanisms that are robust against adversarial attacks.

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

ACM EC'22

Yichi Zhang, Fang-Yi Yu, Grant Schoenebeck and David Kempe

- Build a theoretical framework to study the review process of a conference with focus on how does the conference's acceptance policy affects the tradeoff between the conference quality and the review burden.

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

Under reviewing

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

- Consider how to optimally reward the crowdsoucing workers with the rank-order mechanisms given the noisy measurements of their effort.

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

Under reviewing

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

- Generalize the incentive guarantees to handle a much larger space of untruthful strategies.

COURSES

Computer Science: machine learning, reinforcement learning, approximation algorithm, randomized algorithm. Economics: advanced game theory (mechanism design), electronic commerce, digital public goods.

TEACHING

I'm the teaching	assistant ((GSI)	of the	following	courses:

• SIADS 642: Deep Learning with Prof. Paramveer Dhillon.	Fall 2021
• SIADS 652: Network Analysis with Prof. Daniel Romero.	Fall 2021
• SI 699: Big Data Analysis with Prof. Misha Teplitskiy.	Winter 2022

AWARDS

• The Web Conference Student Scholarship.	2021
• EIC Education Scholarship (top 5%).	2018
• Samsung Scholarship (top 3%).	2017
• Meritorious Winner in Mathematical Contest in Modeling.	2017